Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
- Box: 56, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Getting Acquainted with Sears: Honoring America's Bicentennial; Celebrating Our 90th Anniversary Year - Retail Induction Training, 1976; Publication (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Getting Acquainted with Sears: Central Service Induction Training, Publication (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Opportunities in Credit Sales Management, 1969; Publication (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Think Twice About Sears Management: Careers in Controllership, 1975; Publication (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: Group Life Insurance and Travel Accident Insurance, 1970; Publication (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Box: 56, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Medical Plan for Employees and Their Families, 1973; Publication (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Your Military Leave, 1970; Publication (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Medical Plan for Employees and Their Families, 1974; Publication (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Sears Group Life Long-Term Disability and Business Travel Accident Insurance, 1976; Publication (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Sears Medical Plan for Employees and Their Families, 1973; Publication (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Medical Coverage for Retirees and Dependents, 1970; Publication (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Medical Coverage for Retirees and Dependents, 1970; Publication (Box 56, Folder 7)
- Box: 56, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Savings and Profit Sharing Pension Fund of Sears, Roebuck & Co. Employees - Rules and Regulations, 1971; Publication (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: You and Sears, 1955; Publication (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: The Savings and Profit Sharing Pension Fund of Sears, Roebuck and Co. Employees - Rules and Regulations, 1957; Publication (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: To: Men and Women Considering a Career with Sears, Publication (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Your Group Life Insurance, Publication (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: You and Sears, 1952; Publication (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Think Twice about Sears Professional Data Processing, 1974; Publication (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Think Twice about Sears Credit Sales Management, 1975; Publication (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Attitude Surveys as a Tool of Management, 1950; Publication (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: United States Business Performance Abroad: The Case Study of Sears, Roebuck de Mexico, S.A., 1953; Publication (Box 56, Folder 8)
    Author: Richarson Wood and Virginia Keyser
- Box: 56, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Retirement Plan Part II, 1952; Publication (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Retirement Plan Part II, 1952; Publication (Box 56, Folder 9)
- Box: 56, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Offre d'action aux employs, 1963; Publication (Box 56, Folder 10)
    Language: French.
- Box: 56, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Employee Performance Rating Form, Publication (Box 56, Folder 11)
- Box: 56, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Employee Orientation Program: Conference Leader's Guide, 1969; Publication (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Editors' Guide - for Shell Editors, 1957; Publication (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Editors' Guide - for Shell Editors: Writing Part IV, Publication (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: American Voter: Presidential Election Edition, 1950; Publication (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Disability Benefit Plan Regulations - Employee Booklet, 1950; Publication (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: News Service for Employee Newspapers, 1967; Publication (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: Employee Information Program: Shell Organizations, Benefits and Policies, 1954; Publication (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: News Service for Employee Newspapers, 1960; Publication (Box 56, Folder 12)
- Box: 56, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Employee Orientation Program: Conference Leader's Guide, 1965; Publication (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Oil Industry Centennial Discussion Leader's Guide: Introduction to Film "Corn in Freedom"; Discussion: Future of Shell & Our Industry, 1959; Publication (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: News Service for Employee Newspapers, 1958; Publication (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: News Service for Employee Newspapers, 1956; Publication (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Head Office Management Letter, 1955; Publication (Box 56, Folder 13)
    Author: E.H. Walker
  - Item 6: Revision of News Service, 1956; Publication (Box 56, Folder 13)
    Author: Manager - Employee Communications Department
- Box: 56, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Information Program "Look to the Future", 1956; Publication (Box 56, Folder 17)
    Author: Manager - Employee Communications Department - Head Office
  - Item 2: Boldness Pays Off: Conference Leader's Guide, 1957; Publication (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Shell Management Course: Information for Instructors, 1962; Publication (Box 56, Folder 17)
- Box: 57, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Program for Security: Shell Provident Fund; Shell Pension Plan; Social Security, 1952; Publication (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Shell Provident Fund, 1962; Publication (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Shell Pension Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Program for Security: Shell Provident Fund; Shell Pension Plan; Social Security, 1956; Publication (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Shell Provident Fund (Revised), 1958; Publication (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: College Recruitment Program, Publication (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: A Current Look at Shell, Publication (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Shell Alumni News, 1976; Publication (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Head Office Management Letter: Graphics Standards Function Reconstituted, 1970; Publication (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Head Office Management Letter: The Organization Change, 1970; Publication (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Head Office Management Letter: Technical Computing Center Established; Marketing Staff Appointments, 1970; Publication (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Shell Spotlight, 1950; Publication (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Opportunity with Shell, Publication (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Shell Reports: Solar Energy, 1976; Publication (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Box: 57, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: So You're Moving to New York, Publication (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Employee Orientation Program: Manufacturing, 1960; Publication (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Shell Management Course: Information for Instructors, 1966; Publication (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Shell Management Course: Information for Instructors, 1960; Publication (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Box: 57, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Travelers Insurance Company, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: What Shell Means To You, 1960; Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: What Shell Means To You, 1966; Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Handbook for Employees of Wood River Refinery Including Ryles and Regulations, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: What Shell Means to You - Employee Handbook, 1950; Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Disability Benefit Plan Regulations - Employee Booklet, 1954; Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Survivor Benefit Plan Regulations - Employee Booklet, 1952; Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Hospital Surgical Medical Program, 1956; Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Group Life Insurance Plan - Employee Booklet, 1952; Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Survivor Benefit - Group Life Insurance Program, 1960; Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Box: 57, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Hospital Surgical Medical Program, 1958; Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Survivor Benefit - Group Life Insurance Program, 1960; Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Shell Income Protection Insurance (Including Poliomyelitis Expense Benefits) - Employee Booklet, 1956; Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Major Medical Expense Plan, 1953; Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Hospital Surgical And Medical Plan, 1953; Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Income Protection Insurance (Including Poliomyelitis Expense Benefits) - Employee Booklet, 1950; Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Hospital Surgical Medical Program, 1958; Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Disability Benefit Plan Regulations - Employee Booklet, 1954; Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Income Protection Insurance (Including Poliomyelitis Expense Benefits) - Employee Booklet, 1956; Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Box: 57, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Shell Pension Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Shell Provident Fund, 1962; Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Planning for Retirement, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Planning for Retirement - I. Why Prepare for Retirement?, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Planning for Retirement - II. Finances, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Planning for Retirement - III. Health, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Planning for Retirement - What to Do and Where to Live, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Planning for Retirement, 1958; Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Box: 57, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Program for Security and "Is Your House In Order?", Publication (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Disability Benefit Plan, 1963; Publication (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Shell Hospital Surgical Medical Program - Employees and Dependents, 1963; Publication (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Shell Pension Plan, Publication (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Box: 57, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Creating Job Interest and Satisfaction, Publication (Box 57, Folder 8)
    Author: Tom H. Hurley
  - Item 2: Conference Leaders' Guide for "1952 - Shell's 40th Year", 1953; Publication (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Guide For Techniques of Conference Leadership, 1959; Publication (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Fundamental Concepts of Supervisory Training, 1952; Publication (Box 57, Folder 8)
    Author: Val Jean McCoy
  - Item 5: Employee Training Program: Conference Outline - American Enterprise and Industry, Publication (Box 57, Folder 8)
- Box: 57, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Your Job and Your Pay at Shwayder Brothers, Publication (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: How the Swayder Medical Department Can Help You to Keep Healthy, Publication (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Operation of the Education Refund Policy, 1964; Publication (Box 57, Folder 9)
    Author: M. L. Freed - Director of Industrial Relations
- Box: 57, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Retirement Plan for Salaried Employees of Simplex Wire & Cable Company, 1959; Publication (Box 57, Folder 10)
- Box: 57, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Simmons Hospital and Surgical Insurance plan, 1951; Publication (Box 57, Folder 11)
- Box: 57, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Wage Chronology No. 31: Sinclair Oil Companies, 1957; Publication (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: The Wage Chronology Series: Sinclair Oil Companies, 1941; Publication (Box 57, Folder 12)
- Box: 57, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Our Way of Living, Publication (Box 57, Folder 13)
- Box: 57, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: SK&F News Supplement, 1961; Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: SK&F News Supplement: SK&F Benefits, 1965; Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: SK&F Benefits: Health Insurance Program Includes Hospital, Surgical, Medical, Major Medical Coverage, 1967; Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: How to Make A Gifts-For-Education Program Effective, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
    Author: Frederick H. Osborn, Jr.
  - Item 5: We've Got You Covered, 1957; Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
- Box: 57, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Development Programs for Liberal Arts and Business Administration Graduates - Administration; Finance; International Commerce; Marketing Research; Advertising and Promotion, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: How to Handle the Q & A, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
    Author: Robert Haakenson, PH.D.
  - Item 3: You Are the Next Speaker, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: How to Use Audio-Visual Aids, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
    Author: Robert Haakenso, Ph.D
  - Item 5: How to Read A Speech, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
    Author: Robert Haakenson, Ph.D
  - Item 6: The Art of Listening, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: Conference Leadership Techniques, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Item 8: A Career in Systems Development, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
- Box: 57, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Guide Line Method of Job Evaluation, Publication (Box 57, Folder 16)
- Box: 57, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Pre-Social Security Allowance Plan, 1957; Publication (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Retirement Annuity Plan, 1956; Publication (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Survivorship Benefit Plan for 20-Year Employees, 1957; Publication (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Sickness and Accident Disability Benefits Plan, 1957; Publication (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Total and Permanent Disability Benefits Plan, 1957; Publication (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: Employee Savings Plan, 1957; Publication (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: Termination Allowances Plan, 1957; Publication (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Item 8: Health Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Item 9: Guide for Medical Examiners, 1955; Publication (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Item 10: Group Life Insurance Plan, 1956; Publication (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Item 11: Driver's Handbook, 1958; Publication (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Item 12: So You Want a Better Job, 1955; Publication (Box 57, Folder 17)
    Author: Paul W. Boynton
  - Item 13: Safety in Terminal And Bulk Plant Operation, 1958; Publication (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Item 14: Employees Savings Plan of Socony Mobil Oil Company, Inc., 1955; Publication (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Item 15: A Guide for The Administration of the Socony Mobil Educational Refund Plan, Publication (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Item 16: Recommendations for Administration of the Medical Policy, Publication (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Item 17: Medical Policy, Publication (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Item 18: Home First Aid, 1957; Publication (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Item 19: What and Why of Audio-Visual Aids, 1954; Publication (Box 57, Folder 17)
- Box: 57, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: 1958 Calendar of Employee Development Courses, Publication (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: A Guide for Those Who Plan and Conduct Them, Publication (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: An Approach To Supervisor Development, Publication (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: How To Instruct Principles - For Supervisors, 1954; Publication (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: Salary Administration Guides, 1957; Publication (Box 57, Folder 18)
    Author: M.S. Trumble
  - Item 6: Position Description, Publication (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Instructions for Preparing Position Description, Publication (Box 57, Folder 18)
- Box: 57, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Questions and Answers About Socony-Vacuum's Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Employees Savings Plan, Publication (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Socony-Vacuum's Plan to Share Your Educational Expenses!, Publication (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Socony-Vacuum's Plan to Share Your Educational Expenses!, Publication (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: Preserve Your Health, Publication (Box 57, Folder 19)
    Author: A.E. Hoag, M.D., F.A.C.S., Medical Director
  - Item 6: Every Worker An Investor, 1953; Publication (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Item 7: The Development of People for Key Positions, 1954; Publication (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Item 8: Audio-Visual Varieties, Publication (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Item 9: Tips on Talking, Publication (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Item 10: How To Hold Effective Conferences: A Practical Reference for the Sinclair Guided-Conference Leader, Publication (Box 57, Folder 19)
- Box: 57, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Progress Through Better Management of Human Resources, Publication (Box 57, Folder 20)
- Box: 57, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: You've A Date with Tomorrow, Publication (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Employees Group Insurance, 1954; Publication (Box 57, Folder 21)
- Box: 57, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: How About Your Safety? For Your Protection and Security - Learn The Job The Safe Way, The Right Way, Publication (Box 57, Folder 22)
- Box: 57, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: A Report on Laboratory Training, 1963; Publication (Box 57, Folder 23)
    Author: Boris Gertz, Ph.D.
- Box: 57, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Employees Manual of Safe Practice Standards, Publication (Box 57, Folder 24)
- Box: 57, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Plan for Employees' Pensions; Disability Benefits; and Death Benefits, 1964; Publication (Box 57, Folder 25)
- Box: 57, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Edison Benefit Fund - Rules and Regulations, 1952; Publication (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: Blue Cross: Contracting Hospitals of Hospital Service of Southern California, 1953; Publication (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: Employee Benefit Plans, 1968; Publication (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Item 4: Techniques of Appraising, Publication (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Item 5: Techniques of Appraising, Publication (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Item 6: Counseling, Publication (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Item 7: Management Development, Publication (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Item 8: Personnel Appraisal, 1958; Publication (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Item 9: Personnel Appraisal, 1958; Publication (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Item 10: Circular No. 26: Management Training by the Line Organization, 1962; Publication (Box 57, Folder 26)
    Author: Robert N. Coe
  - Item 11: Endorsement to the Hospital Service Agreement - Series U Endorsement 2UC-D - Family Members Only - Providing Indemnification for Certain Professional Services issued by Hospital Service of Southern California, Publication (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Item 12: Hospital Service Agreement, Publication (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Item 13: Employee Benefits at Southern California Edison Company, 1953-1954 (Box 57, Folder 26)
- Box: 57, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Bulletin of The Institute of Management, 1951-1952 (Box 57, Folder 27)
- Box: 57, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: For Your Security: Group Life Insurance With Double Indemnity For Accidental Death, 1961; Publication (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: Employees' Benefit Plan, 1964; Publication (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - Item 3: Employees' Benefit Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - Item 4: For Your Security: Group Life Insurance With Double Indemnity for Accidental Death, Publication (Box 57, Folder 28)
- Box: 57, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Employee Training - A Booklet To Inspire Employee Courtesy, Publication (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: Group Insurance Protection For You and Your Dependents: Hospital and Surgical Expense Insurance, 1954; Publication (Box 57, Folder 29)
- Box: 58, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Accident and Sickness Insurance; Hospitalization Benefits; Surgical Benefits; Plans, Publication (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: My Plan for Financial Security Prepared for the Employees of Sperry Gyroscope Company Division of the Sperry Corporation, Publication (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Actual Cost - Hourly Paid Labor Plus Fringe Benefits, Publication (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Box: 58, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Retirement Plan for Employees of Sprouse-Reitz Co., Inc., Publication (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Box: 58, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Your Health Insurance Program, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Squibb Retirement Plan, 1951; Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Supervisor's Check List For Introducing a New Employee to His Section and his Job, 1951; Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Introducing The New Employee To The Job, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Box: 58, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Refinery Engineering, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Science & Engineering Careers in Southern California, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Management Opportunities and the MBA, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Careers in California: Chevron Research Company, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: A Job Should Be Exciting, 1867; Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Careers in Engineering, 1975; Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Financial Management and Controllership for MBA Graduates, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: About Jobs, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Professional Careers in Refining, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Careers in Petroleum Marketing, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Careers in Engineering Management, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Professional Careers in Refining, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Careers in Science and Engineering, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Careers in Oil Production, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Box: 58, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Directions: Career Paths with the Chevron Family of Companies, 1975; Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Disability Insurance Plan: A Statement of Coverage, 1967; Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: You and Your Company, 1958; Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Medical Insurance Plan for Employees, 1961; Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Disability Insurance Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Medical Insurance Plan for Annuitants, 1959; Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Disability Insurance Plan, 1963; Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Medical Insurance Plan for Dependents - California Area, 1961; Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Western Division Incorporated As Separate Company, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Standard Oil Company of California Stockholders, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Industrial Relations: Chart, 1975; Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: What You Should Know About Living and Working in Holland, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Professional Careers in Refining, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Engineering Careers in Oil Production, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: Careers in Management and the Professions with Standard Oil Company of California, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: You Career in Oil, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 18: Careers in Oil Production, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 19: Standard Oil Company of California and California Research Corporation, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 20: Engineering Careers in Oil Production, 1975; Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)